사인은
소위의 경동맥에
DUCKY: Cause of death--
a single wound to the ensign's
넓게 생긴 이 상처일세
carotid artery
with a wide blade.
- 왜 소위였을까요?
- 그들은 어린 라이나를
Why the ensign?
Well, they were trying to recruit
다시 돌아오게 하려 했으니
윌트 소위가 방해가 됐을거야
Layna Korkmaz.
Ensign Wilt got in the way.
이 채팅방에 들어오라고
설득 당했었어요
I got talked into joining
this other chat room,
아무도 영화나 음악에
대해서는 이야기하지 않았죠
only nobody there was
talking movies or music.
- 뭐에 대해서 이야기 했어?
- 내가 외롭지는 않은지
What were they talking about?
Asking if I was lonely and...
내 소명을 알고 있는지 물었어요
did I know my calling.
Messages from who?
누구한테서 메세지가 왔어?
- 미친 사람들이요
- 테러리스트 집단이지
The crazy people.
GIBBS: Terrorist group.
채팅방 사이트에 따르면
According to the chat room
support site,
헬벤트427은
브래들리 시멕이에요
Hellbent427 is Bradley Simek.
그 애한테 폭탄이 있어요
컴퓨터에 화약이 묻어 있었고
ABBY: He's got a bomb. The kid
has gunpowder on his computer,
플라스틱 기폭장치의
도면을 가지고 있었어요
and a blueprint
for a plastic detonator.
- 기폭장치를 프린터 했다구요
- 안돼!
He printed a detonator.
GIBBS: Don't!
번역 : 엉이
솵 NCIS 12x23 솵
The Lost Boys
Original Air Date on May 5, 2015
수정, 배포 금지
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
10분이요
Ten minutes.
뭐?
What?
선배가 그렇게
생각하고 있죠, 안 그래요?
That's what you're
thinking, right?
제 말은, 10분만 빨랐다면
아이가 집을 떠나는 걸
I mean, ten minutes earlier,
and we could've stopped him
막을 수 있었다고요
from ever
leaving his house.
이런 일은 일어나지도 않았겠죠
None of this
would've happened.
5분이라고 생각하고 있었어
I was thinking five.
병원에선 부상이 많지 않대요
Hospital listed all
other injuries as minor.
더 나쁠 수도 있었겠죠
Could've been worse.
16살 꼬마가 버스에서
폭탄 자살을 했어
16-year-old kid blows himself up
on a bus,
맞아, 더 나빴을 수도 있겠지
and it could've been worse.
네
Yeah.
아이의 어머니에겐
연락드렸어요
All right, Simek's
mother's been notified.
아이가 사실대로 말했다고
생각하세요?
You think he was being
straight with you?
누구?
Who?
아이요, 시멕 말이에요
The kid. Simek.
자기가 윌트 소위를 죽이지
않았다고 했잖아요, 그 말 믿으세요?
Said he didn't kill Ensign Wilt.
We believe him?
컴퓨터 맞은 편에 앉아있는
어떤 개같은 자식이
Some sick bastard
on the other end of a computer,
아이를 세뇌시켰어
putting ideas
into kid's head.
그 자식을 어떻게
잡을지 알아내
You tell me how we get
a hold of that guy!
도니가 사이버팀이랑
같이 작업중이에요
Dorney's into it
with Cyber.
최대한 빨리 보고해!
I want a full report ASAP!
알겠습니다
Roger that.
됐어요, 제가 맡을게요
Okay, I got it.
박사님
Duck.
아이가 폭탄을 터뜨렸을 때
Uh, the boy's right
arm was obliterated
오른쪽 팔이 완전히 날아갔어
when he detonated the bomb.
나머지 부분들은
저기에 있네
The rest of his mutilated
body ended up there.
하지만 아이가 어떻게든
설득을 당했어
But he was convinced
somehow, in all of this,
자신의 죽음이 품위있는
죽음이라고 말일세
that there was dignity
in his martyrdom.
- 어서 아이를 내보내죠
- 이상하군
Let's get him out of here.
Strange.
- 뭐라고요?
- 이상해
What?
Strange.
아이의 팔에 있는
이 그림들을 보게
These marks
on his arm.
불에 탄 자국인 줄 알았는데
가까이서 보면
I noted them as burns,
but on closer inspection,
패턴이 보여
they appear to be
in a pattern.
- 문신인가요?
- 그럴 수도 있지
A tattoo?
Possibly.
그래, 뭔가 낯이 익어
Yeah, this design is familiar.
죄송합니다, 부인
TONY:
Hey, excuse me, ma'am.
노란선 밖으로 물러..
이봐요!
Behind the yellow... Hey!
선 뒤로 물러서세요!
Get behind the tape!
What are you thinking?
왜 그러세요?
뭘 보셨어요?
What happened?
Did you see something?
모르겠군
I don't know.
안녕
Hi.
안녕하세요
Hello.
뭐하고 있어?
(laughs)
What you doing?
MTAC으로 들어가려고요
I'm about to head into MTAC.
아, 맞아, 깁스가
보고하라고 하셨지
Oh, that's right, 'cause Gibbs
asked for that cyber update.
맞아요
McGEE:
That's right. Wow, so,
MTAC에서 보고만 하는게 아니라
you're not only doing
쇼 전체를 맡고 있는거야
your first MTAC briefing.
You are running the show.
네, 안에서 봐요
Yup. I'll see you in there.
아, 난 안에 안 들어갈거야
Oh, I'm not going in there.
좀 무서운 곳이잖아
Place is scary.
팀이 나중에 다시
나한테 보고할 거야
Tim will give me
an update later.
충고를 좀 하자면
나 같으면 들어가기 전에
And a word to the wise--
I would empty my bladder
화장실 한 번 들릴거야
before I go in there,
엄청나게 무서운 곳이잖아
'cause it's the scariest
place on Earth.
들어갔던 요원들이
제대로 버티는 걸 본 적이 없거든
We've seen good agents
wet themselves bad.
진짜야
카펫에 자국도 있잖아
It's very true.
And the carpet stains, so...
Look, guys,
저기, 선배들
충고는 고맙지만
괜찮아요
I appreciate the pep talk,
but I'm fine.
이런 상황은 이제
저한테 별 문제 없거든요
Stressful situations
don't get to me anymore.
- 언제부터?
- 좋아요
Since when?
Okay.
전 자신감 있는 사람이고
선배들한테 도움이 될 지도 모르니까
I'll tell you this because
I'm confident enough to do so,
but, also, because
it might help you, too.
이걸 알려 드릴게요
이 말을 기억하세요
Two words:
또 다른 자아
alter ego.
압도되는 기분이 들 때마다
Whenever I'm feeling
overwhelmed,
머릿속에서 더 나은
나를 끄집어내는 거에요
I mentally transition
into a better version of myself.
비욘세랑 샤샤 피어스처럼?
You mean like Beyonc챕
and Sasha Fierce?
전 클라크 켄트랑 슈퍼맨을
I was thinking more like
떠올렸는데 뭐,
비슷한 거에요
Clark Kent and Superman,
but, yeah, same idea.
멋진데
That's fantastic.
맞아요
It is.
방금 선배들이 오기 전에
더 나은 나를 끄집어 냈어요
I transitioned
right before you walked up.
그래서 선배들의 거짓말이
저한테 안 통하는 이유죠
That is why your B.S.
is not getting to me.
그래서 우리가 지금
얘기하고 있는게 누구야?
So, right now, who
are we talking to?
MTAC에서 아주 잘 해낼
특수요원 길로이 립스죠
Gilroy Libbs, Super Agent,
ready to kick some MTAC ass.
Huh.
홍채 스캐너는 껌이죠
First time with the eye scanner.
Child's play.
방금 하는 거 봤어?
Did you see him do
that eye scanner?
난 처음 들어갈 때
14번이나 했었는데
First time I did it--
14 tries.
길로이 립스란 사람
좀 멋진데요
Gilroy Libbs is kind of awesome.
그래
Yeah.
NCIS 사이버 팀이
브래들리 시멕의 대화에서
NCIS Cyber linked Bradley
Simek's communications
몇몇 익명의 모집자를
찾아냈습니다
to several anonymous
recruiters.
이름을 알아와
I want names.
곧 알아낼 겁니다
And we'll get them.
현재로선 그 모집자들을
For now, we were able
to tie the recruiters
특정 테러 집단으로
묶을 수 있었습니다
to a specific terror cell.
부통령님?
Vice President?
도너겟 요원이 우리를
MAN: Agent Dorneget
brought us together
테러 집단에 대한 정보를
공유하기 위해 불렀습니다
to pool our Intel on the cell.
결국엔 전세계적으로
퍼질 위험이 있는겁니다
After all, this is
an international epidemic.
지금 저희가 이야기하고
있는 집단이 상당히
MAN 2: Group in question
is gaining notoriety
악명을 떨치고 있는 상황입니다
under a number
of calling cards worldwide.
(speaking foreign language)
통역하자면
"더 콜링"입니다
Or simply translated:
쏷he Calling.
- 지금 어디 있습니까?
- 중심 조직은 이라크에 있지만
Where are they?
HASSAN: The heart of the cell is in Iraq,
범위는 굉장히 좁고
제한적입니다
but their reach is unlimited
and focused.
MAN 1:
Calling is making a strong push
콜링은 아이들을 모으는 데
매우 주력하고 있습니다
to recruit children.
- 인터넷에서요
- 맞아요
On the Internet.
Exactly.
채팅방을 개설하거나
They're employing chat rooms,
총게임이라던지
만화까지 동원하고 있어요
first-person shooter games,
even cartoons,
10살까지 어린 아이들을
무기화시키고 있는거죠
in an effort to weaponize
children as young as ten.
더 어린 아이일 수록
덜 위협적으로 보일겁니다
The younger they are, the
less they look like a threat.
조직의 미션은 뭡니까?
And the cell's mission?
그들 자신을 약자로 인식해서
They see themselves
as underdogs,
자신들을 억압하는 사람에게
대항하는 겁니다
standing against
their oppressors.
근본적으로 보자면 콜링은
잃어버린 아이들을
Essentially, The Calling is
a twisted Peter Pan
국제적으로 모집하는
변질된 피터 팬인거죠
recruiting an international band
of Lost Boys.
- 좋은 비유네
- 고마워요
It's a good metaphor.
Thank you.
인터폴이 긴급히 콜링이
인터넷에서 아이들을
SALI: Interpol is assembling
an emergency think tank
모집하는 걸 막기 위해
to create a plan
to stop The Calling's
싱크 탱크를 만들고 있습니다
online recruitment of youth.
새로운 정보가 들어왔어요
GIRARD: May I interrupt
with a development?
말씀하세요
Go.
프랑스에 있는 콜링의
We've sent you background
리더에 대한 정보를 보냈습니다
on a Calling leader
here in France.
조직 내에서의 연락을
할 수 있게하는 사람이고
He does facilitate communication
within the cell.
이름은 매튜 루소에요
His name is Matthew Rousseau.
그를 주시하는 중입니다
We're looking at him.
미국에서 이 자에게 보내는
My team has intercepted
몇몇의 메일들을
several e-mails to him
중간에서 가로챘어요
from the United States.
위치 파악 됬습니까?
Do you have a location?
아뇨, 하지만 몇몇 내용을
알아낼 수 있었어요
No, but we were able to decrypt
some content. It appears
미국 내에 있는 몇몇 조직원들이
several Calling loyalists
in the U.S.
암시장에서 S-마인을
구입하고 있다더군요
are seeking S-mines
on the black market.
무슨 뜻이죠?
Meaning what?
S-마인, 도약식 지뢰라고도 불리는데
ABBY:
An S-mine, or a Bouncing Betty,
제2사세계대전 때 독일이
지뢰로 사용한 폭탄이에요
was a land mine used
by Germany in WWII.
건들리면 하늘로 솟아서
공중에서 터지는 거죠
When triggered, it shoots into
the air, and then, it detonates.
- 파편으로 하는 샤워 같은 거에요, 깁스
- 나도 알아, 앱스
It's like a shrapnel shower, Gibbs.
I know what it does, Abbs.
아직도 구할 수 있는지
알고 싶은거야
I want to know
if you can still get 'em.
물론이죠, 제 말은
Yeah, I mean, if you have,
아주 무서운 친구가 있으면요
like, a really scary friend.
소름끼치고 구석을 좋아하는
Like a super creepy,
corner-lurking,
- 그런 친구말이에요
- 왜 이런 일을 벌이는 거지?
black-market friend.
Why go to the trouble?
제가 아는 건 콜링이
S-마인을 그렇게 원한다면
All I know is, if The Calling
wants these S-mines so bad,
단지 북엔드로 쓰려는
I don't think
they're gonna use them
이유는 아닐 거에요
for, like, bookends.
이걸 찾는 사람들을
어떻게 찾아내지?
How do we find the guys
that are looking for them?
I was hoping you had an idea.
깁스한테 계획이
있길 바랬는데요
(sighs)
계획 있으시죠, 안 그래요?
You have an idea, don't you?
아니
No.
무서운 친구는 있지
But I got a scary friend.
깁스 요원님
Agent Gibbs.
이렇게 다시 뵙게 되서
정말 기쁘네요
How wonderful
to see you again.
좀 힘들어 보이시는 군요
I must say, you're looking
handsomely tortured as ever.
와인이 마시고 싶었는데 말이죠
I had my heart set
on a wine list.
감자 튀김이 더 나을거야, 바야
I highly recommend
the fries, Bayar.
그럼 제가 이렇게 말하겠죠
"부탁입니다, 저희는
So, now comes the part
where I say, 쏱lease,
많은 걸 함께 겪었잖습니까
쐗e've been through
too much together.
아가라고 부르세요"
그럼 당신이 끄덕이고
Call me Agah. You nod,
그러고 나서 재미없는
얘기에 웃으면서 있겠죠
and then, we both smile
at something that isn't funny.
그건 넘어가지
Let's skip that.
동감이에요
긍정적인 얘기로 넘어가죠
Agreed. Now to a positive.
전 당신을 용서했습니다
Which is... I forgive you.
과거에 당신이 저를 좀
힘들게 했었지만
You've hurt my feelings
in the past,
용서는 정신 건강에 좋으니까요
but absolution's good
for the soul.
I'm looking to make a deal.
거래를 하고싶네
바라던 바죠
I'd hoped.
독일제 S-마인을 찾는 사람이
암시장에 있네
German S-mines are being chased
on the black market.
누가 찾는지 알아내는 중이지
I want to know
who's doing the chasing.
제가 안다고 생각하시는 군요
And you think I can tell you.
자네가 찾을 수 있을거야
I think you can find out.
암시장의 무기들은..
자네 분야잖나
Black-market weapons--
that's your wheelhouse.
제 주변에 있는..
사람들은 당신을 닮았습니다
The people in my, uh...
wheelhouse are like you.
지략 있고
심술궃고 무장했죠
Resourceful,
sour and armed.
제가 질문을 한다면
다시 되돌릴 수 없습니다
If I ask a question,
I can't take it back.
당신의 목숨은 당신 몫이지
제게 아닙니다
Your neck is your concern,
not mine.
조건은 똑같을 거야
The terms will be fair.
자네는 DIA와 일했을 때와
똑같이 받게 될거야
You'll be paid the same
as when you work with the DIA.
Okay.
좋습니다
그럼 말해보시죠, 깁스
So, tell me, Gibbsey.
당신이 악마와
거래하는 걸까요
Are you making a deal
with the devil,
아니면 저일까요?
or am I?
(music playing)
Ducky?
박사님?
어서 오시게나, 제쓰로
Oh, hello, Jethro.
You get a new 45?
새로 사신 거에요?
아뇨, 깁스
제 연구실에서 가져왔어요
No, Gibbs.
It's my Lab Jams.
못 알아보시겠어요?
Don't you recognize it?
여기서는
Not in here.
애비와 내가 잠깐동안
같이 일하고 있었네
Yes, well, Abby and I have
joined forces for a moment.
나한테 적당한 음악이
She was kind enough
to show me
얼마나 힘이 넘치게
만들어주는지 보여주고 있었어
how energizing a little bit
of bass can be.
깁스도 원하시면
Yes, sir!
I could totally hook you up
그렇게 해드릴 수 있어요
with some Lab Jams for
the squad room if you want.
- 괜찮아
- 알았어요
No.
Okay.
그럼 그냥 눈부시게
해드리는 건 어때요?
Then how about
we just dazzle you?
그래, 그거 좋군
Yeah, I like that.
그러면 여기에
관심이 있겠군
Yes, well, might I draw
your attention to...
브래들리 시멕의 팔에
있던 디자인일세
the design on
Bradley Simek's arm.
이건 문신이 아니라
영구적인 그림이에요
ABBY: It's not a tattoo.
It's permanent marker.
그리고 각도로 보면
자기가 직접 그린 거에요
And the angle suggests that
he drew it on there himself.
어디서 본 건지는
알아내셨어요, 박사님?
You remember
where you saw it, Duck?
그래
Yes.
전직 육군인 랜달 화이트
Former Army Specialist
Randall White.
그가 4개월 전에
If you recall,
자신의 동료 2명과 같이
four months ago,
he and two of his colleagues
방문했던 이맘을
암살하려고 었지
tried to assassinate
a visiting imam.
- 미국인이었죠
- 맞아요
They were Americans.
ABBY: Yeah.
하지만 시리아에 있는
테러 집단 때문에
But they were radicalized
급진파가 된 사람들이었죠
by a terror cell in Syria.
이건 내가 랜달을 부검할 때
This is one of the autopsy
photographs I took
찍었던 그의 팔 사진일세
of White's identifying mark.
진짜 문신이지
It's a real tattoo.
시멕이랑 똑같은 디자인이네요
GIBBS:
Same design as Simek's.
그리고 브래들리 시멕이
인터넷에서
Now, remember, Bradley
Simek's detonator
기폭장치 도면을
다운받았고
was downloaded
from the Dark Web,
3D프린터로 만들었었죠
and then, it was created
on a 3-D printer.
랜달이 자살할 때
Just like the plastic gun
썼던 플라스틱 총처럼 말이지
that Randall White used
to kill himself.
깁스, 콜링은
Gibbs, The Calling
시리아에서 미국인 3명을
모집했던 것에
is connected to
the same group
분명 연관이 있어요
that recruited the
three Americans in Syria.
화이트는 죽었어
나머지 둘은 어딨지?
White's dead.
Where are the other two?
카일 나자리는 두 달전에
감옥에서 죽었고
Well, Kyle Nasry died
in prison two months ago.
3번째 테러리스트는
The third terrorist...
아직도 잘 살아있지
is very much alive.
보스
BISHOP:
Gibbs.
비숍
사라 구드를 데려 와
Hey, Bishop,
bring in Sarah Goode.
인터폴이 현재 싱크 탱크를
만들고 있는건 알겠지
Gentlemen, as you know, Interpol
is assembling a think tank.
자네가 NCIS 대표로
나가줬으면 하네
I would like you
to represent NCIS.
둘 다 말이야
Both of you.
어디로 가면 되나요?
Okay, where
we headed?
GID 장교 하산이 정한
The sessions will be hosted
카이로에서 회담이 열릴 거야
by GID Officer Hassan
in Cairo.
이집트요?
(laughs)
Egypt?
비행기는 2시간 안에 떠날 거야
Plane leaves in two hours.
(chuckles)
말한 것 같군
Well, it looks like
you told him.
네
Yeah. Wow.
그런 자리에 NCIS를
대표하는 건 정말 영광이죠
Repping NCIS on an international
platform is a huge honor.
- 그럴 자격 있어
- 감사합니다, 제가..
Deserved.
Thank you. I...
죄송해요
너무 흥분했네요
Excuse me. I got excited.
- 도니, 뭐하는 거야?
- 생각하지 않고 있었어요
Dorney, what are you doing?
I wasn't thinking.
길로이 립스가 됬어야 했는데
I should've been
more Gilroy Libbs.
길로이 립스가 누구야?
Who is Gilroy Libbs?
No one.
아무도 아니에요
그럼, 카이로로 갑니다
감사합니다
Okay. Off to Cairo. Thanks.
(door shuts)
그렇게 보지 말게
Don't like that look.
무슨 일이 일어나고 있어요
Yeah. Something's come up.
바야는?
Bayar?
그게, 거래가 성사되지
않을 것 같습니다, 깁스
Yeah, the deal
isn't gonna fly, Gibbs.
DIA가 눈치를 챘어요
거래를 중단했습니다
DIA got wind of it.
They shut it down.
- 리온, 그들이 결정할 문제가 아니야
- 아니요
Yeah. It's not their call.
But it is.
국방 장관이 뒤를 봐주고 있어요
SecDef is backing them.
바야는 이미 두 개의
작전에 참여하고 있구요
They got Bayar locked
into two ops already.
- 협조하길 바라지 않아요
- 국장
They don't want him compromised.
Director,
우린 그가 필요해
we need him on this.
끝났습니다, 깁스
It's done, Gibbs.
아가 바야를 이용할 수 없어요
Using Agah Bayar is a no go.
콜링에 대해서 이야기 해보죠
I want to talk to
you about the Calling.
- 저랑 연관짓는 건가요?
- 네
You connected them to me?
Yes.
- 실망스럽네요
- 이봐요
That's disappointing.
TONY: Look,
우리가 비밀스러운 테러리스트
이야기를 좋아하는 것 만큼이나
as much as we all love
crypto-terrorist talk,
당신이 콜링에 대해 아는 걸
우리도 알아야 해요
we need to know everything
you know about The Calling.
- 그러니 얘기하는 게 어때요?
- 더 말할게 없어요
So what's it gonna take to get there?
We're already there.
콜링은 제가 시리아에서
들어간 조직의 일부로 시작됐지만
The Calling began as part
of the group I joined in Syria.
좀 다르게 변했죠
But it became
something else.
- 어떻게요?
- 혼란을 가져오길 원했어요
What?
A faction eager to bring chaos.
우리의 정치적 신념은
중요하지 않았죠
They pushed
our religious doctrine aside.
그들은 권위를 거부하고
They're rooted in nothing but
the desire to reject authority
시스템을 마비시키길 원했어요
and paralyze the system.
아이들을 현혹시켜서 말이죠
Misguided youth...
내부 당파들이 갈라지고
따르는 사람들을
The faction broke off
이라크로 데려갔어요
and moved its followers to Iraq.
그리고는 곳곳에 있죠
And now they're
everywhere.
그늘을 드리우는
방법 밖에 없어요
Overshadowing
the one true way.
저도 당신들 만큼이나
그들을 멈추고 싶어요
I want them stopped
as badly as you do.
어떻게 하면 도울 수
있는지 말해주세요
Just tell me how to help.
조직에 있는 사람들
이름을 알려줘요
Names. Anyone who's a member.
저희 조직은 어린 아이들을
다시 되찾고 있어요
Our group is winning back
young people by the day.
집으로 돌아갈 방법을 찾은
사람들을 노출시킬 순 없어요
I can't risk exposing those
who've found their way home.
이 목록들은
These are
몇몇 콜링의 모집자들과
브래들리 시멕이라는 소년과
chat room discussions between
several Calling recruiters
했던 대화 내용이에요
and a boy named
Brad Simek.
이틀 전에 버스에서
폭탄을 터트려서 자살했어요
Kid blew himself up
for the cause two days ago.
이 이름 알아요
I know this screen name.
SS빌더-48.
SS_BUILDER-48.
- 누구죠?
- 저희와 잠시동안 있었는데
Who is it?
He was with us for a time
콜링으로 넘어간 사람이에요
but was wooed by The Calling.
똑똑한 기술자였죠
He's a brilliant engineer--
a prodigy.
그는 자신의 정서적 성장보다
연구가 더 중요했어요
His emotional growth took
a backseat to his studies,
그래서 아이들을 관련시켰죠
그는 영향력 있는 모집자였어요
so he relates to youth.
He's a powerful recruiter.
그는 자기 자신을
'빌더'라고 불렀어요
He called himself
The Builder,
폭탄을 만들고 사람들을
모았으니까요
a builder of bombs
and of a people.
진짜 이름은 뭔지 알아요?
Do you know
his real name?
"SS"는 사디크 사말을 뜻해요
The 쏶S stands for Sadiq Samar.
그게 그의 진짜 이름이에요
That's
his real name.
그를 찾게 된다면..
If you find him...
끝장내버리세요
end him.
좋아요, 여기 있어요
TONY:
Okay, here we go.
사디크 사말은 25살에
현재 미국에 거주하는 미국 시민권자고
Sadiq Samar, 25.
U.S. citizen and resident
Pied Piper for the Calling.
콜링의 피리 부는 사나이죠
(아이들을 모은다는 의미)
공학 기술에서 19살에
Got his master's degree
in engineering
석사 학위를 취득했어요
at the ripe old age
of 19.
2년 전에 미국의
외국인 정책에 대해
He was arrested two years ago
during a protest
반대 시위에 참여했다가
체포된 적이 있어요
of U.S.
foreign policy.
- 지금 어딨어?
- 모르겠어요, 일을 안하고 있거든요
Where is he now?
No idea. Doesn't hold down a job.
그의 마지막 주소가
최근 신혼 부부가
But his last known address
was an apartment building
퍼그 세 마리와 함께
임대한 아파트 빌딩이에요
that is now being rented
by a newlywed couple
and their three pugs.
- 뭔가 찾았습니다
- 말해 봐
Got something.
Go.
작년에 살 로버츠란 사람이
Last year,
a Sal Roberts purchased
워싱턴에서 작은 빌딩
하나를 구입했는데
a small building in DC.
계약금이 사말의
은행 계좌에서 지불됬어요
Down payment came out
of Samar's bank account.
그리고 이 로버츠라는 남자의
기록은 더 이상 찾을 수가 없구요
And I can't find any other
record on this Roberts guy.
사말이 가명으로
건물을 산거군요
Samar bought the building
under an alias.
- 주소는 찾았나?
- 네
You got an address?
Got it.
출발하지
Let's go.
위층은 깨끗해요
Upstairs is clear.
어떤 장소를 비밀로
유지하는 건 좋은 일이지
It's always nice when someone
keeps a place up to code.
It's a bayonet.
총검이야
시멕의 집에 있던
다른 하나인 것 같네요
Looks like the others
from Simek's house.
마른 피가 묻었있네요
BISHOP:
It's dried blood.
윌트 소위를 살해할 때
쓰인 것 같아요
Could be the weapon
used to kill Ensign Wilt.
브래드가 자신이 죽인 게 아니라고
했던 게 사실일 수도 있겠네요
Maybe Brad was telling the truth
when he said he didn't do it.
브래드가 사말에게 칼을 주고
사말이 더러운 짓을 한 걸까요?
Brad gives the knife to Samar,
Samar does the dirty work.
잃어버린 아이들이라..
Lost boys...
(shuffling in distance)
연방 요원이다!
Federal agents!
괜찮니?
You all right?
이제 안전해
이리 나오렴
You're safe.
Come on out.
총이에요
Gun.
버스 사고 현장에 있었지
You were at the bus.
이름이 뭐니?
What's your
name, son?
Whoa.
아저씨한테 줄래?
You want to hand that to me?
좋아, 내가 그리로 갈게
Okay. I'll come to you.
천천히
Easy.
그대로 있으렴
Stay where
you are.
천천히
Nice and easy.
괜찮아, 잡았어
Okay. Got it.
됐어
Clear.
집 타이를 써, 비숍
TONY: Use the zip
ties, Bishop.
수갑을 채우기엔
너무 작으니까
He's too small for handcuffs.
루크 해리스, 맞지?
Luke Harris, right?
어젯밤에 부모님께서
실종 신고를 하셨단다
Your parents reported you
missing last night, Luke.
빌딩에서 뭘하고 있던거니?
What were you doing
in the building?
사디크 사말이란 남자를 아니?
You know a guy by the
name of Sadiq Samar?
있잖아, 나도 이야기하는 거
별로 안 좋아해
You know, I don't
like to talk either.
말을 너무 많이하면
사람들은 말하지 않은 걸
You talk too much,
people end up thinking
듣게 되거든
they heard things
you never said.
네가 이야기하지 않으면
널 도와줄 수가 없어
But if you don't speak up,
I can't help you.
네가 무슨 일에 관련있든 간에
다시 되돌릴 수 있어
Whatever you got mixed up in,
you can turn it around.
혼자서 생각해보렴
Think for yourself.
네가 선택하는 거야
Make a choice.
이 아이는 그냥
꼬마인데 말이죠
BISHOP:
He's just a kid.
- 뭘 알아냈지?
- 애비가 총검이
What have we got?
Abby confirmed the bayonet
윌트 소위를 살해하는 데
쓰인 칼이라고 확인했습니다
was used to kill Ensign Wilt.
피 묻은 부분 지문이
사말과 일치해요
Partial print in blood
was a match to Samar.
냉혹한 살인자가 자신의
이력서에 경력을 쌓는 거죠
Cold-blooded killer. The Builder
is adding to his r챕sum챕.
이 아이에 대해서
이야기해 봐
I want to hear
about this kid.
이름은 루크 해리스고
버지니아의 그레이트 폴에 사는
Luke Harris. Wendy and David
Harris of Great Falls, Virginia,
부모가 어젯밤에 실종 신고를 했어요
양부모구요
reported him missing last night.
They are his adoptive parents.
아이의 생물학적 부모는
이라크 출신인데
His biological parents were
originally from Iraq but fled
첫번째 걸프전 이후에
터키로 망명을 갔어요
to Turkey
after the First Gulf War.
아이가 태어나자마자
입양 보냈구요
TONY: Put him up for adoption
shortly after he was born.
애비가 경찰서에서
노트북을 가져왔는데
BISHOP: Uh, Abby got his laptop
from the police,
지금 다른 일을 하고 있어서
but she was pulled
into something else,
저희보고 보스한테
읽어드리라고 했어요
so she asked us
to read you her findings.
읽어 봐
So read 'em.
알았어요
Yep. Okay.
"깁스, 깁스, 깁스
깁스, 깁스"
쏥ibbs, Gibbs, Gibbs,
Gibbs, Gibbs.
어..
Uh...
"루크가 사말이랑 다른
콜링의 조직원들과 함께
쏬uke was communicating with
Samar and other Calling members
온라인 채팅방에서 대화를
하고 있었어요, 클릭"
in a new chat room
on the Dark Web. Click"
아, 클릭해야지
Oh, click.
"TOR 또는 어니언 루터라고
알려진 방화벽이
BISHOP:
쏛 tool known as TOR,
누가 사이트에 접속했는지
쐎r the Onion Router,
makes it impossible
알아내지 못하게 하고 있어요"
to track who's
accessing the site"
내가 필요한 정보로 넘어가지
Skip to the part I care about.
세상에, 애비가 보스가
그 말을 할 거라는 걸 알고 있었어요
Oh, my God. She knew
you were gonna say that.
정확히 글자 그대로에요
바로 여기
Word for word.
Right there.
- 적혀있어요, "내가.."
- 맞아요
It says, 쏶kip...
Yeah.
Uh...
Oh.
"강화된 보호 때문에 사말이
새로운 채팅방을 만들었어요"
쏤or added protection, Samar
constantly hops to new chat rooms.
"이 새로운 채팅방은
벌써 사용되지 않고 있어요
쏧n fact, this new chat room
is already inactive.
"로지타 수녀님의
볼링 게임처럼요, 깁스
쏧 mean, it's as dead as Sister
Rosita's bowling game, Gibbs.
지난 주에 엉덩이 수술을
받으셨거든요"
She had hip surgery
last week. Oh.
"더 이상 없어요, 클릭"
클릭
쏣nd of findings.
Click. Click.
채팅방 내용을 쭉 살펴봤는데
BISHOP: We combed through the chat
room's content. It confirms
버스가 터지고 난 직후에
Luke learned
about Simek bombing the bus
시멕이 그랬단 걸
루크가 알았어요
shortly after it happened.
궁금해서 현장에 있었던 거겠지
He was at the crime scene
because he was curious.
그러고 나서 사말이 루크에게
빌딩으로 가서
Later, Samar told Luke to go
to the building to...
"네 형을 만나"라고 했죠
쐌eet his brothers.
깁스, 루크는 어떻게 사말과
연락해야 하는지 알거에요
Gibbs, Luke has to know
how to contact Samar.
이야기 하도록 만들어야 해요
We need to get him to talk.
오셨어요, 깁스
아깐 제가 너무 바빠서
Hey, Gibbs. I'm really bummed
that I wasn't there
제가 찾은 걸 보고드릴
수가 없었어요
to report my findings
to you earlier,
다른 걸 찾느라고 바빴거든요
but I was busy
finding other findings.
우산은 왜 들고 있어?
What's with the umbrella?
파피 아시잖아요
You know Poppy.
제 양산이라구요
She's my parasol.
제가 건물을 나갈 때마다
She goes with me every time
I leave the building
항상 저랑 동행한다구요
이건 조금 이따 다시 보구요
and go outside. But we'll
get back to her in a minute.
첫번째로, 제 친구인
에밀리오 에반스가
First, I want to talk to you
about my friend Emilio Evans.
워싱턴에서 크레스트웰
역사적 사회에서 일하고 있어요
He works for the Crestwell
Historical Society in DC.
- 그게 어때서?
- 그는 균형잡힌 얼굴을 가지고 있어요
What about him?
He has a perfectly symmetrical face.
저를 좀 설레게 만들었죠
Kind of blows my mind.
그래서 엄청나게 유용한
역사적 자료에 접근할 수 있어요
And he has access to a lot
of useful historical documents.
뭘 찾았는데?
What'd you find?
사말이 빌딩을 샀을 때
완전히 난장판이었어요
When Samar bought the building,
it was in shambles.
원래 가격보다 더 많은
돈을 지불하고 구입했죠
He paid way more for
it than it was worth.
에밀리오가 이유를 찾아냈어요
And Emilio and his
snowflake face found out why.
빌딩에 있는 지하가
The basement of the building
1940년대의 벙커 옆에
지어져 있었어요
was forged next to a
bunker from the 1940s.
아직도 있지
It's still there.
그래서 벙커가 아마
좀 고쳐졌겠지만
So the bunker itself
has probably seen its share
아직도 있죠
of renovations but still.
사말이 숨겨진 공간 때문에
Samar bought the place
- 건물을 샀던거군
- 맞아요
for the hidden storage.
Yeah.
그 벙커에 얼마나 많은
법의학적 보물이 있는지
I mean, there's no telling
how many forensic gems
아무도 모를 거에요, 깁스
are in that bunker, Gibbs.
그리고 제가 얼마나
And you know how much
비밀의 방을 좋아하는지
아시잖아요
I love secret rooms.
너랑 파피가 그 벙커에
가고싶어 하는거군
You and Poppy want to leave
the lab and go to the bunker.
토니랑 비숍을 데려갈게요
I'll take Tony and Bishop
with me.
(speaking Arabic)
You speak Arabic?
That's amazing.
아랍어도 해?
놀라운 걸
비행기에서 주요 표현들을
좀 외웠죠
I learned some key phrases
on the plane.
- 체크인 할 시간이 있을까?
- 네
You think we got time to check in?
Yeah.
인터폴이 새 일정을
다시 보내왔어요
Interpol forwarded
a new itinerary.
첫번째 회의가
1시간 내에 있을 거에요
First meeting's
in an hour.
매튜 루소를 기억하실 테죠
You will remember
Matthew Rousseau.
콜링의 통신 담당이죠
McGEE: The Calling's Director
of Communications.
여러 리더들 중 한 명이에요
One of their many leaders.
아직도 DGSI가 그를
감시하고 있는 건가요?
Is DGSI still
surveilling him?
아뇨
No.
그를 잡았습니다
We got him.
당신들의 특수 부대와
It was a joint operation
함께 협동 작전으로 말이죠
with your special forces.
즉흥적이었지만
정말 대단했어요
Impromptu.
A beautiful thing, really.
루소는 현재 보르도에 있고
He was captured in Bordeaux.
비스케이만에 있는
Currently,
he's being transported
미국 항공 모함으로
수송될 거에요
to a U.S. aircraft carrier
in the Bay of Biscay.
2005년에 샌프란시스코에서
우체국을 폭탄으로
He's wanted in the U.S.
for a... attempted bombing
터트릴려고 했어요
of a post office
in San Francisco in 2005.
그래서 미국으로 수송
중에 있는 겁니다
Which is why he's being
transported back to the States.
호위가 필요한거군요
So he's gonna need an escort.
맞아요, 그리고 그를
수송기에서 심문할 때
Yes. And I'll bet that escort
will get first crack
가장 먼저 그를 심문할 겁니다
at interrogating him
on the carrier.
뭐하세요?
What are you doing?
내가 지원하려고
I am volunteering
for the job.
다 됬어
TONY (grunting):
Almost.
뭐라고요? 크게 말해요
여기선 잘 안들린다고요!
What? You guys, talk louder!
I can't hear you back here!
거의 다 열었대요
He said he
almost has it open!
좋아요, 안에 보여요?
뭐가 보여요?
Okay, can you see anything?
What do you see?
안에 뭐 있어요?
What's in there?
- 비밀의 방에 뭐가 있어요?
- 애비
What's in the secret room?
Abby,
조용히 해봐
quiet.
인내심을 가지라고
Have a little patience.
방이 괜찮은지 확인되면
As soon as we
clear the room,
와서 볼 수 있게 해줄게
비숍, 따라와
we will invite you to look.
Bishop, follow me.
깨끗해요!
Clear!
여기서 무슨 일이 있었던 거죠?
BISHOP:
Whoa. What happened in here?
폭탄을 터트린 거에요
They bombed it.
괜찮다고 들어서
바로 달려왔어요
I heard you say 쐁lear,
so I just ran in
어..
그게.. 치타처럼요
like a...
like a... like a cheetah.
이건 파편이에요
This is shrapnel.
그래
Yeah.
(grunts)
테스트하는 장소인 것 같은데
Some kind of test site.
여기있는 이 구멍의 크기가
The dimension of these holes
S-마인과 거의 일치해요
match the specs for an S-mine.
여기에 심어서
They were planted
터트린 거죠
and then they
were detonated.
이것 좀 봐요
Look at this.
무슨 문서 같은데요
Some kind of document.
도식의 부분인 것 같네
This looks like
part of a diagram.
원통이 선으로 연결되있어
The cylinders
connected by a line.
사말은 똑똑했으니
폭탄들을 어떻게
Samar's handy.
Could be figuring out how to
연결할 지 알았겠지
connect the mines.
그래서 그가 여기서
폭탄 두 개를 한번에 터트린 거에요
That's why he tested
two at once in here.
폭탄들을 더 강력하고
He's modifying them
into a huge,
치명적인 도약식 지뢰로
만든 거에요
mean Bouncing Betty
on steroids.
그리고 더 많이 필요했겠죠
And he has to have more.
그럼 나머지는 다 어디로
가져간 걸까요?
Then where'd he take
the rest of them?
저희는 루크를 낳으신
분들을 뵙지는 못했어요
We never met
Luke's biological parents.
완전히 낯선 두 사람이
It's hard to believe
that two complete strangers
인생에서 가장 큰 선물을
줄 수 있다는 건 믿기 힘든 일이죠
can give you the greatest gift
of your life.
루크한테 언제부터
문제가 있었습니까?
When did Luke start
having trouble?
2년 전부터요
About two years ago.
하룻 밤 사이에
일어난 것 같아요
It seemed like it
happened overnight.
학교 친구들이 루크가
중동에서 왔단 걸 알았고
Kids at school found out
he was Middle Eastern.
루크를 괴롭히기 시작했어요
They started
to tease him.
우린 걱정이 되서
루크의 노트북을 봤었죠
We were worried,
so I looked at his laptop.
그가 방문했던 사이트들과
이야기를 나눈 사람들을 봤어요
I saw the sites he was visiting,
the people he was talking to.
그 사람들은 루크에게..
They were telling him that...
루크에게
They were telling him
아이가 겪는 고통은 미국인처럼
행동하기 때문이라고 하더군요
that all his pain was from
pretending to be American.
상담사에게 루크를 데려갔었어요
WENDY: We took him
to a therapist.
아이는 점점..
점점 괜찮아지고 있었죠
He was getting...
He was getting better.
괜찮아, 괜찮아
DAVID:
It's okay, it's okay.
어제쯤 갑자기 심해졌어요
Yesterday, it got bad.
학교 아이들이 루크의 사물함에
나쁜 말들을 적었다고 하더군요
Kids at school spray-painted
some ugly words on his locker.
루크는 집에 와서는
방을 엉망으로 만들었어요
He came home,
destroyed his room...
이미 늦은 뒤에
저흰 그 사실을 알았죠
We didn't know
until it was too late.
루크는 이미 나가고 없었죠
He was already gone.
이전에 루크는 어땠습니까?
Who was Luke
before all this?
아이의 물건이 여기 있어요
These are some of his things.
경찰이 아이의 방을 살폈는데
The police already
processed his room.
대부분은 망가졌지만
He destroyed
most of it, but
침대 밑에 있는 건
멀쩡하더군요
he missed what was
under the bed.
깁스 요원님, 요원님 이전엔
루크가 이전에 어떤 아이었는지
Agent Gibbs, you're
the first person to ask
물어보는 사람은 없었어요
what he was like before.
제가 찾는 아이가
누군지 알아야 하니까요
Got to know who I'm looking for.
다시 아이를 데려오실 수 있나요?
So you can bring him back to us?
저희 아들이에요
He's our baby boy.
아침을 저녁으로
먹는 걸 좋아한다 더구나
I heard that you like
breakfast for dinner.
팬케이크 만드는 거엔
영 재주가 없어서
I'm not much good
at pancakes.
여기가 아저씨 집인가요?
Is this your house?
그래
Yup.
전 아저씨를 거의 쏘려고 했는데
Why would you bring me here
왜 저를 여기로 데려오신 거에요?
when I almost shot you?
그랬니?
Did you?
Oh.
Well...
날 쏘길 원했던 사람들 대부분은
lots of people who
wanted to shoot me
이 집에 온 적이 있단다
have been in this house.
(laughing)
안 먹을거라면, 루크
If you're not gonna eat, Luke,
우유는 다시 냉장고에 둬야지
milk goes back in the fridge.
두 번은 안 물을거야
I'm not gonna ask again.
나도 딸이 있었어
I had a daughter.
네가 앉았던 의자에
앉아있곤 했었지
She used to sit right there
at the table where you were.
언젠가 한번 내 주머니 칼을
딸 아이가 가져간 적이 있었어
She took my pocket knife
from me once.
칼은 장난감이 아니었고
딸 아이는 그걸 알고 있었지
Knife wasn't a toy,
and she knew that.
여기로 올라와서는
She climbed up here.
칼을 들고서
And she took that
knife and she
캐비넷 뒤에다가 자기
이니셜을 새겼지
carved her initials right into
the back of that cabinet, there.
그리고 나서는 내가 아끼던
그 칼을 잃어버렸어
Then she lost the best
pocket knife that I ever had.
어떻게 했어요?
What'd you do?
물론 혼냈지
Oh, I scolded her.
외출 금지도 시켰고
Grounded her.
그리고는 용서해줬어
Then I forgave her.
전 아무것도 아니에요
I'm nothing.
전 아무것도 아니라고요!
I'm nothing!
모두가 날 싫어해요!
Yeah, everyone hates me!
그냥 절 죽여요!
Just kill me!
그게 그 사람들이 원하는거고
내가 원하는 거에요!
That's what they want,
that's what I want!
그들은 독일제 S-마인을
선택했죠
German S-mines were chosen
for their manufacturing.
최신 모델보다는
Desired changes
were easier to implement
바꾸기가 쉬웠을 테니까요
than with the later models.
슈토양이 벙커의 도식을
분석했는데
Ms. Sciuto analyzed
the schematics from the bunker.
암호화된 Wi-Fi로
As many as six mines
6개 정도의 폭탄이
연결돼 있었다고 하더군요
will be linked
via encrypted Wi-Fi.
트립와이어와 정확한 레이저를
Tripwire's virtual.
가상으로 표현한 겁니다
A pinpoint laser.
자네 아버지의 지뢰는 아니군
Not your dad's land mine.
No.
사말의 벙커에서
두 개의 폭탄이
Well, there was
evidence of two mines
터진 증거가 있습니다
detonated in
Samar's bunker.
지금쯤 더 가지고 있겠죠
By now he could have more.
- 그리고 아이는?
- 루크 해리스는
And the boy?
Luke Harris.
방어적인 태도를 취하고 있는데
He's back
in holding.
사말과 연락할 방법을
알고 있는 것 같습니다
Likely knows how
to get in touch with Samar.
- 가망이 없는 아이인가?
- 아니, 가망이 없는 게 아니야
Lost cause?
No, he's not a lost cause.
시간이 좀 필요한 것 뿐이지
It'll take some time
to turn him around.
그러지 마세요
Don't have it.
DGSI가 다량의 통신 내역을
가로챈거 기억하시죠?
Remember, DGSI intercepted
multiple communications.
사말 혼자서 미국 땅에서
Samar is not the
only Calling member
S-마인을 가지고 있는게
아니란 말입니다
stockpiling S-mines
on American soil.
이 게임에서 우리는
가능한 많은 사람이 필요합니다
We need a line to anyone
and everyone in the game.
우린 바야가 필요해
We need Bayar.
DIA가 허락하지 않을 겁니다
DIA won't budge.
저희가 조사를 좀 했습니다
We did some digging.
바야가 매주 금요일마다
한 아파트로 식료품을 보내고 있어요
Bayar sends groceries to
an apartment every Friday.
그의 어머니가 그곳에
비밀리에 살고 계시죠, 이상하죠?
His mother lives there
in secret. Go figure--
아가 바야에게
어머니가 있어요
Agah Bayar has a mother.
그 자는 어머니가 추방
당하는 걸 원하지 않을거야
He won't want her deported.
우린 공명정대한 거래가
필요한게 아니야
We don't need
an aboveboard deal.
'우리를 돕도록 바야를 협박하고
DIA는 모른다'
Blackmail Bayar to help us,
DIA's none the wiser.
그게 계획입니까?
That's the plan?
그래
더 좋은 게 있나, 리온?
Yeah. You got
a better one, Leon?
충고를 드리자면
A word of advice:
들키지 마십쇼
don't get caught.
난 루크랑 같이 있으니
디노조, 네가 바야를 맡아
Hey, I'm with Luke.
DiNozzo, you're with Bayar.
드디어 그를 만나는 군요
Finally gonna meet
the pride of Turkey.
그 자는 널 별로 좋아하지
않을거야, 비숍을 데려가
Yeah, well he's not gonna
like you. Take Bishop.
정말 맛있네요
These are to die for.
이야기 좀 하죠
We need to talk.
새로운 친구를 만드는 걸
좋아하는 만큼
As much as I adore
making new friends,
난 오래된 친구를 잃는
것을 걱정하는 사람입니다
I worry about
losing old ones.
깁스가 곤경에 빠졌어요
Gibbs is tied up.
어떻게 생각해요?
What do you think?
그녀가 어떻게 생각하냐니
무슨 뜻이죠?
What do you mean
what does she think?
깁스가 곤경에 빠졌고
우릴 보냈어요
Gibbs is tied up,
he sent us.
당신 말을 들었지만
I heard you.
대답이 마음에 들지 않는군요
But I didn't
like your answer.
대답이 마음에 안 드는 거에요
아님 내가 싫은 거에요?
You don't like my answer
or you don't like me?
둘 다요
Neither.
깁스가 정말 곤경에 빠졌어요
Gibbs really is tied up.
- 사과의 말을 전해달래요
- 봤죠?
He sends his apologies.
You see?
부드럽게 말하니까
She dips it in sugar,
달콤하게 들리잖아요
and all of a sudden,
it tastes so sweet.
바야씨..
Mr. Bayar...
아가라고 부르세요
Please, call me Agah.
아가
Agah.
당신 어머니에 대해
이야기 좀 하죠
We'd like to discuss
your mother.
깁스와 내가 서로
동의한 일입니다
Gibbs and I had an agreement.
저희도 압니다
We know.
공평한 조건에 대해
합의를 봤다구요
We shook on fair terms.
그럴 일은 없을 겁니다
Not gonna happen.
DIA 때문인가요?
DIA?
중요한 건
The problem is
저희가 아직 당신의
도움이 필요하단 거에요, 아가
we still need
your help, Agah.
당신이 주변에 연락을 해서
We need you to reach out
to your contacts
누가 S-마인을 찾고 있는지
알려줬으면 해요
and find out who's
seeking these S-mines.
이 사람들의 위치를
파악해야 합니다
We need locations
on these people.
좋습니다, 내 나름대로
Yes, well, I did some research
조사를 좀 해봤어요
of my own, dear heart.
당신들은 콜링을 쫓고
And I know that
you're after The Calling,
콜링은 아이들을 쫓고 있죠
and The Calling's
after the children.
맞아요
That's right.
제 어머니는 결함이 있지만
My mother's flawed,
제 어머니입니다
but she's my own.
만약 한 번만 더
내 어머니를 협박할 시에는
And if you ever
threaten her again,
민주적으로 나가지 않을 겁니다
my response
won't be civil.
도와주죠
I'll help you.
당신들이 한 노력은
낭비였어요
But your efforts
were wasted.
난 대가 없이도
당신들을 도왔을 겁니다
I would've helped you
without payment,
협박도 없이요
and without blackmail.
- 왜죠?
- 여자와 아이가 먼저니까요
Why?
Women and children first.
이건 우리가 항상 동의하는
절대적인 규칙이죠
It was an absolute
we could always agree upon.
아이들이 전쟁에 이용될 땐
When babies are used
in the wars of men...
신이 우리 모두를 도울 겁니다
...then God help us all.
박사님
(door opens)
Duck...
- 괜찮으세요?
- 이 아이에게 중요한 어떤 게
you all right?
Well, seeing what once mattered
그를 매우 진실되고
어리게 만들었네
to Luke Harris makes him
very real, very young.
짧은 시간 안에
현혹된 아이를 프로파일링 하는게
This is my second profile
of a manipulated boy
벌써 두 번째일세
in just a short number of days.
이전엔 그냥 문제가
좀 있는 아이었어요
Before, it was just
one troubled kid.
지금은 젊은이들에게 영향을
끼치는 바이러스를 보고있지
And now we see a virus
affecting our youth.
내 말은, 왜
I mean, why
루크의 불만이 그를
여기까지 오게 했느냐는 거야
did Luke's frustrations
bring him here,
집을 뛰쳐나가고
instead of storming
out of the house
담배를 피우는 것
대신에 말이야
and lighting up
a cigarette?
모든 십 대들은
반항을 하기가 쉽다네
Every teen
is prone to rebellion.
그래
Yeah.
하지만 콜링이
But then The Calling
그 취약함을 테러를
저지르게 만들어 버린거지
twists that vulnerability
into terror.
박사님, 전 이 아이를
알아야만 해요
Duck, I got to reach this kid.
사말을 찾으려면 말이지
To find Samar.
루크 자신과
부모님을 위해서에요
For himself,
for his parents.
그리고 자네를 위해서도
For you.
도움이 될 만한 걸
찾은 것 같네
I think I've found
something that might help.
애비가 인터넷에서
콜링의 포럼에서 나온
This grotesque reading
is from The Calling forum
이 터무니없는 것들을 찾았어
that Abby found
on the Deep Web.
모집된 아이들을 위한
사말의 안내서 같은 거지
It's a virtual handbook
from Samar to his recruits.
여기엔 그들이 자신의
충성심을 보이려면
It tells them that in order
to demonstrate their loyalty,
그들 자신들의 옛날 삶을
포기해야한다고 적혀 있네
they must give up
their old lives.
루크가 집을 나가기 전에
방을 엉망으로 만들었었죠
Luke trashed his room
before he left.
하지만 사말에 따르면
모집되기 위해서
But according to Samar,
the most important act
가장 중요한 건
콜링의 이념에
for a recruit is
to condemn those
함께하지 않는 자들을
비난하는 걸세
who are not aligned with
The Calling's ideology.
특히 자신과 가장
가까운 사람들에게 말이야
쏣specially those
closest to you.
부모님이군요
His parents.
그래, 그래서 이 공책을
Yeah. Which brings me
좀 더 살펴봤네
to this notebook.
이건 루크가 직접 쓴 거야
Now, this is Luke's handwriting.
편지에요?
A letter?
그의 양부모님에게 쓰는 편지지
To his adoptive
parents.
언어가 굉장히 공격적이야
The language
is brutal.
하지만 편지를
끝맺지는 못했어
Yeah, but the letter
is unfinished.
부모님과 의절하려고 했었군요
He was trying to disown 'em.
끝낼 수가 없었을 거야
He couldn't bring
himself to finish it.
제쓰로, 여기 보이는 이 어둠은
Jethro, the darkness here
부정할 수 없는 걸세
is undeniable.
하지만 우리가 마주하고 있는 건
But what we're
dealing with is a...
어린 아이일 뿐이야
well, it's a child.
이 모든 것 뒤에는
Who, beneath it all,
장담하건대 아이는
부모님을 많이 사랑하고 있어
I swear, he-he loves
his parents very much.
네가 쓴 거야?
Did you write that?
- 네가 쓴 거냐고!
- 네
Did you write that?!
Yes.
내가 보여주기 전에
끝맺고 싶니?
You want to finish it
before I show it to 'em?
- 누구한테요?
- 네 부모님한테 말이다
To who?
Your parents.
뭐가 문제야?
What's wrong?
부모님한테 쓴거잖아, 그렇지?
It's for them, isn't it?
넌 네가 해야했던
것들을 다 했어
You did everything
you were supposed to.
콜링이 아닌 사람들과
연을 끊으면서 말이야
Disown everyone who
isn't The Calling.
- 그게 사말이 원했던 거야, 그렇지?
- 제발
That's what Samar wants, right?
Please don't
- 부모님께 보여드리지 마세요
- 아니, 이미 결정된 거야
show it to them.
Oh, no, that's already been decided.
- 안 돼요, 알았어요? 안돼요!
- 이봐!
Don't, all right? Don't!
Hey!
죽고싶다고 말한 건 너야
You said you
wanted to die.
부모님이 그 말을
들으면 어떤 기분이겠어?
What would your parents
think if they heard that?
네가 부모님을 아프게 했어
You broke their hearts.
학교에 있는 아이들은
나를 싫어해요
The kids at school hate me.
이라크로 돌아가라면서요
They kept telling me
to go back to Iraq.
더 이상 어떻게 해야할지
모르겠단 말이에요
I don't know
what to do anymore.
나한테 얘기 해
You talk to me.
Where is Samar?
사말 어딨어?
내가 아는걸 얘기해 주면..
If I tell you what I know...
부모님 보러갈 수 있어요?
will you take me
to see my parents?
그래
Yes.
난..
I... (sighs)
부모님을 슬프게하려고
했던 게 아니에요
I didn't want to hurt them.
난..
I...
부모님이 슬퍼하길
원하지 않아요
I don't want to hurt them.
빌딩에서 뭘 하고 있던거야?
What were you doing
in the building?
루크는 사말이 시키는 대로
그 빌딩에 있었던 거였어요
Luke was in the building because
Samar ordered him to stay there.
루크가 얘기했어?
Gibbs got Luke to talk?
루크는 그의 형이라 불리는
Okay, so, Luke went to
the building to meet up
사람을 만나러 갔지만
with his so-called brothers,
사말은 둘이 만나기 전에
모든 사람들을 내보냈어요
but Samar got everyone out
before their introductions.
브래들리 시멕의 컴퓨터 때문에
He was afraid that
Bradley Simek's computer
경찰이 빌딩으로 올까봐
겁이났던 거죠
would lead the police
back to the building.
- 근데 왜 루크한테 있으라고 한거죠?
- 왜냐면 경찰은
Then why tell Luke to stay behind?
Because Samar knew
아이를 쉽게 쏘지 않을테니까요
that the police would
hesitate to shoot a kid.
함정이었네요
It was a trap.
우리가 루크를 찾았을 때
When we found him,
쏠 수 있는 사람 누구든지
쏴야했단 말이에요?
Luke was supposed
to kill whoever he could?
맞아요, 하지만 좀 더
긍정적인 부분을 보자구요
Yeah, but let's focus on
the positive here, though.
이건 사말이 최근에 만든
채팅방의 주소에요
Like the URL
for Samar's latest chat room.
루크가 깁스에게 줬어요
Luke gave it to Gibbs.
봐요, "요즘 L이 어떻게
생각하는지 아는 거 있어?"
Look: 쏦ave you heard
how Little L is feeling"
루크에 대해
이야기하고 있었겠죠
They've got to be talking
about Luke.
맞아요, SS빌더-48
Yeah, SS_BUILDER-48.
사말이 이야기하는 거에요
That's Samar talking.
"L이 감기에 걸린 것 같아
쏧 think Little L has the flu.
일을 하지 않았어
아니면 우리가 소식을 들었겠지"
He didn't go to work, or we
would have heard about it"
"일을 하지 않았어"
쏡idn't go to work.
일을 안했다는 건
아무도 죽이지 않았다는 거에요
Didn't do his job--
he didn't kill anyone.
(sighs)
"아픔에 굴복하면
BISHOP: 쏦e needs to
learn what happens
어떤 일이 생기는지
알려줘야겠어"
when you give in
to the sickness"
이 사람들은 루크를
배신자로 생각하고 있어요
They think Luke's a traitor.
- 루크가 위험해요
- 지금 어디있어요?
He's in danger.
Where is he?
깁스가 부모님
집으로 데려갔어요
Gibbs took him
to his parents' house.
문이 열려있어요
The door's open.
이봐, 이봐
Hey. Hey!
여기에 있어
Stay here.
엄마!
LUKE:
Mom!
엄마! 엄마!
Mom! Mom!
아빠!
(crying):
Mom! Mom! Dad!
아빠! 아빠!
Dad! Dad!
아빠!
Dad!
GIBBS: Hey, hey, hey.
엄마!
안돼, 안돼!
(gasping, screaming):
Mom! No! No!
S-마인에 대해서는
아무것도 모릅니다
I know nothing
about any S-mines.
DGSI는 네가 콜링의
리더라고 생각하던데
Well, DGSI thought that
you were a Calling leader.
언론은 네가 그저
하인이란 걸 알게되면
Guess the press is gonna have a
field day when they find out
온종일 떠들어 대겠지
that you're only a lackey.
미국에 대해 물으셨죠
You ask about
the United States.
질문이 잘못됬어요
You ask the wrong questions.
그럼 그냥 바로 알려주지 그래?
Then why don't you
set me straight?
큰 파티를 계획할 때
When you plan
a big party,
많은 세부사항들이
여러 군데서 의논되죠
there are many details
discussed over many lines.
비밀로 유지하는 건 불가능 해요
It is impossible
to keep them secret.
나랑 있으려고 그런 파티를
놔두고 오다니요
You left such a party
to be with me today, no?
재미있는 걸 놓쳐서
미안하게 생각해요
I'm sorry you're missing
our contribution to the fun.
경비원!
Guard!
문 열어요!
지금 당장 전화해야 해요!
Open up! I need a phone!
NED:
McGee.
맥기 선배
잠깐 쉬는 중이에요
방금 막..
Hey, we're on a break.
I was just about to...
도너겟, 내 말 잘 들어
McGEE: Dorneget, listen to me.
호텔에 위협이 있어
그들이 네가 거기 있는 걸 알아
There's a threat to the hotel.
They know you're there.
거기 있는 사람들 모두
내 보내야 해, 최대한 빨리
You need to get everyone out
of there. Evacuate now!
모두 나가요! 어서!
Everybody out! Go! Go!
- 무슨 일이죠?
- 호텔에 위협이 있어요, 가세요
What is happening?
Threat to the hotel. Go.
어서 나가요! 어서!
Go! Go!
(shouting in Arabic)
나가세요!
(speaking Arabic)
Go!
(speaks Arabic)
(speaking Arabic)
안돼요, 안돼요, 안돼요!
No! No! No! No! No!
40분 전에 카리오의 시내에 있는
ZNN REPORTER: Once again, we bring to you
the latest on the explosion
알 마하라는 호텔에서
that occurred
less than 40 minutes ago
폭발이 또 한번 있었습니다
at the Hotel Al Maha
in downtown Cairo...
알겠어요, 그의 상태가
확인되면
All right, I need you
to call me back
최대한 빨리 연락 주세요
감사합니다
as soon as you know his status.
Thank you.
다른 소식 없어?
Anything?
- 기다리고 있는 중이에요
- 아이랑 같이 있어요
I'm on hold again.
GIBBS: Stay with him.
같이 있어줘야 해요
He needs somebody with him.
도너겟은?
Dorneget?
마지막으로 들은 건
병원으로 급히 이송되었답니다
Last we heard, he was
rushed to the hospital.
계속 소식을 기다리는 중이에요
We're waiting on an update.
- 맥기는?
- 카이로로 돌아가는 중이에요
McGee?
He's circling back to Cairo.
다른 요원이 루소를
여기로 데려오고 있습니다
The agent afloat's escorting
Rousseau back here.
보스, 루소는 폭발에 대해
Boss, Rousseau
had prior knowledge
미리 알고 있었어요
여러 개의 폭탄이 레이저
of the explosion.
The Intel suggests
트립와이어로 연결되어
있었답니다, 이건 콜링 짓이에요
multiple mines with a laser
tripwire. This was The Calling.
터트리기 전까지
그냥 시간 문제였겠죠
It's just a matter of
time before they take credit.
- 어디까지 알아냈어?
- 뭘 말입니까?
Where are we?
With what?
아무 거든, 디노조!
이 일의 주동자를 알아 내라고
With anything, DiNozzo!
I want the head of this thing!
누구야?
무슨 일을 꾸미는 거냐고?
Who is he?
What is his play?
우리가 여기라고 알고있을 때
왜 카이로를 공격한 거야?
Why is he hitting Cairo
when our Intel says here?
- 보스
- 뭐야?
Gibbs.
What?
방금 전화를 받았어요
I just got confirmation.
도너겟이 버티질 못했답니다
Dorneget didn't make it.
바야랑은 어떻게 되가고 있어?
Where are we with Bayar?
줄 게 있다고
만나잡니다
He has something for us,
wants to set a meet.
그럼 가서 만나
Then do it!
줄 게 뭐죠?
All right, what do you have?
I'll wait for Agent Bishop.
비숍 요원을 기다리죠
(sighs)
지금 통화 중이에요
She's on the phone.
네, 보이는 군요
Yes, I can see that.
이봐요, 내가 오늘
안 좋은 날을 보냈거든요
Look, I haven't had a great day.
날 싫어하는 거 알아요
I know you don't like me.
그냥 얘기하면 안될까요?
Can we move on?
Agent DiNozzo,
예민하게 굴지 말아요
don't be so sensitive.
이 작은 공간에
빛나는 두 마리의 종마에요
Two shining stallions
in one tiny area.
우리가 함께 있으면
When we're together,
세상의 안정이
불균형 해지거든요
the world's stables
are knocked off-balance.
(sighs)
죄송해요
Sorry about that.
S-마인을 찾고 있는
세 명의 신분을 확인했어요
I have identified three
people seeking S-mines.
자세한 내용은
안에 있을 겁니다
The particulars
are inside.
카이로는 단지 시작일 뿐이에요
Cairo is just
the beginning.
- 오늘 밤 있었던 폭발은 테스트였어요
- 뭘 위한 테스트죠?
The attack tonight was just a test run.
Test run for what?
콜링이 모든 주요 도시에서
The Calling are gathering
S-mines
S-마인을 모아들이고 있어요
in all major cities
around the world.
그들은 합동으로 국제적인
공격을 계획하고 있어요
They are planning a coordinated,
international attack.
만약 성공한다면
If they succeed,
그 결과는 재앙일 겁니다
the results will
be catastrophic.
그게 언제죠?
When?
그건 모릅니다
I have no idea.
계속 조사해주시길
바랄게요, 아가
BISHOP: We need you to
stay on this, Agah.
계속 알아봐 주세요
We need you to keep digging.
저도 한계는 있습니다
I have my limits.
무료는 오랫동안
즐길 수 있는게 아니니까요
Pro Bono only feels good
for so long.
엎드려요!
Down!
(grunting)
(groaning)
구급차가 필요해요
He needs an ambulance.
괜찮아요
BISHOP:
Okay. It's okay.
세부 사항들이 새고 있어요
Details are trickling in.
바야는 수술 중에 있고
Bayar's in surgery.
의사는 긍정적이랍니다
Doctors are optimistic.
카이로 까지
As far as Cairo,
해군 장관님께 알렸습니다
I did speak to SecNav. She...
깁스?
Gibbs?
제 얘기를 들으세요
I need you with me.
여기 있어
I'm here.
해군 장관님께는 보고 드렸습니다
Reports to SecNav are confirmed.
도너겟 요원이 잠깐동안
사람들을 대피시켰어요
Agent Dorneget led
a last-minute evacuation.
많은 사람들의 목숨을 구했죠
He saved a lot of lives.
그도 당신이 알아주길
원했을 겁니다
He would have wanted you
to know that.
His family?
가족은?
It's just his mother.
어머니 뿐입니다
She's been notified.
어머니껜 연락 드렸고
She's been out of the country.
- 여행이란 건 복잡하니까요
- 그렇지
Travel is complicated.
Right.
우리가 해줄 수 있는 건 없나?
There anything
we can do for her?
네, 있습니다
Yeah, actually, there is.
어머니께선 카이로에서
비행기가 도착하기 전까지
She won't be able to make it
돌아오시지 못할 것 같습니다
before the plane arrives
from Cairo.
우리가 갈 거야
Well, we'll be there for him.
(sighs)
장례 절차
집중!
COMMANDER:
Funeral detail, attention!
Forward... march!
앞으로 가!
"우리는 항상 젊음을 위해
미래를 개발할 수는 없지만
DUCKY: 쏻e cannot always build the
future for our youth.."
미래를 위해 우리의 젊음을
개발할 수는 있다."
...but we can build our youth
for the future.
루스벨트의 명언은 더 이상
절실하지 않지
FDR's words were
never more urgent.
Gibbs, you all right?
보스, 괜찮으세요?
GUARD COMMANDER:
Shoulder arms!
앞으로 가
GUARD COMMANDER:
Forward march.
We weren't expecting you
until tomorrow.
내일 오실 줄 알았는데요
- 저희가 기다렸을 텐데요
- 압니다
We would have waited.
I know.
깁스?
Gibbs?
CIA 장교 조아나 티그입니다
CIA Officer
Joanna Teague,
도너겟 요원의 어머니시죠
Agent Dorneget's mother.
티크 장교님
GIBBS:
Officer Teague,
조의를 표합니다
we're sorry for your loss.
네드는 분명히
고마워 했을 겁니다
Ned would have appreciated
the pomp and circumstance.
하지만 제 아들은 죽었고
But my son is dead,
범인은 아직 밖에서
돌아다니고 있으니
and his killers
are still out there.
우리가 해야할 일이
있는 것 같군요
I'd say
we've got some work to do.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man